♪♪
- Okay, boys, our annual camping trip
好了，孩子们，我们和朋友们一年一度的露营之旅终于到了，
with our friends is finally here,
而且我们都知道这意味着什么。
and we all know what that means.
——恐怖之夜比赛。
- The scare night contest.
——女生对男生。
- Girls versus boys.
——还有终于有机会赢得恐怖泰迪奖杯。
- And the chance to finally win the Teddy of Terror trophy.
现在，我知道我们都试着忘记去年发生的事，
Now, I know we've all
但我们别忘了去年发生的事。
tried to forget what happened last year,
——好了，让惊吓开始吧！
but let's not forget what happened last year.
——好吧，伙计们，
- Okay, let the scaring begin!
- 好了，吓人开始！
- All right, guys,
- 好的，伙计们，
all we have to do is stay strong
我们只需要在接下来的五个小时里保持坚强，然后我们——
for the next five hours, and we--
- 小丑威格索给你做了一只贵宾犬！
- Wigso the Clown made you a poodle!
[所有人尖叫]
[all screaming]
[所有人笑]
[all laughing]
- 好吧，我们比去年大了一岁
- Well, we're a year older
现在更难被吓到了。
and a lot harder to scare now.
- 贵宾犬时间！
- It's poodle time!
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
[laughs]
[笑]
Don't worry, Teddy of Terror.
别担心，恐怖泰迪。
You'll be coming home with the girls again this year.
今年你又会和女孩们一起回家。
- Oh, no, this year, the boy's have something
- 哦，不，今年，男孩们有
really scary planned.
真正吓人的计划。
- Like Dicky in a hockey mask waving a toilet brush?
- 像迪基戴着曲棍球面具挥舞马桶刷？
- Hey, Mom wouldn't let us use the chain saw last year.
- 嘿，妈妈去年不让我们用链锯。
- And the same goes this year.
- 今年也一样。
boys: Aw, man!
男孩们: 哎，伙计！
- Anne, can I see you in the kitchen
- 安妮，我能和你去厨房
for a little powwow? - Sure.
开个小会吗？ - 当然。
- In private.
- 私下里。
[kids scream] And no eavesdropping.
[孩子们尖叫] 不要偷听。
It's rude, and you always mishear things anyway.
这很无礼，而且你总是听错。
[sighs]
[叹气]
I didn't want to scare the kids,
我不想吓到孩子们，
but there's a wild animal on the loose at the campground.
但露营地有一只野生动物在逃。
[all gasp] - He said there's a wild animal
[大家都惊呼] - 他说有一只野生动物
riding a moose making a cramp sound.
骑着麋鹿发出痉挛的声音。
- Wait, are you sure he didn't say,
等等，你确定他没说，
"There's a wild animal on the loose
“营地里有只野生动物在逃？”
at the campground?"
我知道我听到了什么。
- I know what I heard.
让我听听。
- Let me listen.
而且那动物在吃松鼠。
- And the animal's eating squirrels.
（惊呼）那动物在吃女孩？
- [gasps] - And the animal's eating girls?
或者是松鼠。
- Or squirrels. - He knows what he heard.
他知道他听到了什么。
- So we're gonna have to cancel the camp out.
所以我们得取消露营了。
- You can't make us dance till the lamp's out!
你不能让我们跳舞直到灯熄灭！
both: Yeah!
是的！
- Or cancel the camp out.
或者取消露营。
- See, this is why your dad said, "No eavesdropping."
看，这就是为什么你爸爸说，“不要偷听。”
- Well, you were talking about our campout.
嗯，你们在谈论我们的露营。
- And we know what we heard.
我们知道我们听到了什么。
- No, you don't.
不，你们不知道。
- Did you decide to cancel the campout?
你们决定取消露营了吗？
- Yes.
是的。
- Because of a wild animal?
因为野生动物？
- Yes. - And is this wild animal
是的。
also riding a moose making cramp sounds?
也在骑着麋鹿发出抽筋声？
- Aha! No.
- 啊哈！不是。
- What your father said is that the campground is not safe
- 你父亲说露营地不安全
and we're gonna have to cancel.
所以我们得取消。
- But if we cancel, the girls keep
- 但如果我们取消，女孩们就会
the Teddy of Terror trophy for another year.
再保留一年恐怖泰迪奖杯。
- Sorry, campground's off-limits,
- 抱歉，露营地禁止进入，
unless there's another place that's got lots of room
除非有另一个地方有很多空间
and camping gear that we can get last minute.
和露营装备，我们可以临时获取。
- You mean like Tom's Get Sporty?
- 你是说像汤姆的Get Sporty？
- Huh...
- 嗯...
Ah, my Get Sporty would work.
啊，我的Get Sporty会管用。
all: Yes!
大家: 太好了！
- Thanks, Mom. Thanks, Dad.
- 谢谢妈妈。谢谢爸爸。
Get ready to lose again this year.
准备好今年再次输掉吧。
- [scoffs] I don't think so.
- [嗤之以鼻] 我不这么认为。
Boo!
嘘！
- Really?
- 真的吗？
- She's right. Balloon animals aren't scary.
- 她说得对。气球动物并不吓人。
[pop, boys scream]
[啪，男孩们尖叫]
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Okay, go easy on the spray glue, Tom.
好的，喷胶别用太多，汤姆。
It's pretty sticky.
这胶水很黏。
- I think I know how to use glue, Anne.
- 我想我知道怎么用胶水，安妮。
- Welcome to the annual Teddy Bear of Terror campout.
- 欢迎来到年度恐怖泰迪熊露营活动。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Yeah! - All right.
- 耶！ - 好的。
The rules are pretty simple.
规则很简单。
First team to scream loses,
第一个尖叫的队伍就输了，
and then the girls take the bear home.
然后女孩们可以把熊带回家。
- Oh, really? What if you guys lose?
- 哦，真的吗？如果你们输了怎么办？
- Boo. [all gasp]
- 嘘。[所有人惊呼]
[all laughing]
[所有人笑]
- The scaring starts when the full moon rises.
- 当满月升起时，吓人游戏就开始了。
All right, time to go set up camp
好了，是时候去搭帐篷了
and start preparin' the scarin'.
并开始准备吓人。
- Okay, girls are in the camping section.
- 好的，女孩们在露营区。
- And boys are in the winter sports section.
- 而男孩们在冬季运动区。
- Okay, I'm gonna go get started on the hot dogs.
- 好的，我要去开始准备热狗了。
- Ah, you're on the dogs,
- 啊，你在负责热狗，
I'm on the dog groomers next door.
我接下来要去隔壁的狗狗美容店。
- Do you still think they're filling our dumpster
- 你还是认为他们在用我们的垃圾桶
with their trash? - I don't think.
装他们的垃圾吗？ - 我不只是认为。
I know,
我知道，
and I am gonna prove it.
我要证明这一点。
[grunting]
[咕哝]
Ah!
啊！
Gah!
嘎！
- All right, guys,
- 好了，伙计们，
let's go over the plan again.
我们再过一遍计划。
Natlee and I made some creepy dolls.
Natlee和我做了一些吓人的娃娃。
- And I brought some voice recorders.
- 我还带了一些录音机。
- Which we'll tape to the dolls,
- 我们会把这些录音机粘在娃娃上，
hide them all around the store,
1. 把它们藏在商店各处
and make the dolls say scary stuff.
2. 让玩偶说恐怖的话
- I've been working on the voice.
3. 我一直在练习声音
[clears throat]
4. [清喉咙]
[angrily] I will...eat...
5. [生气地]我要……吃掉……
your...soul!
6. 你的……灵魂！
[roars]
7. [吼叫]
- That's pretty good.
8. - 挺不错的。
Let me try it.
9. 让我试试。
[in demonic voice] I'm gonna rip out your heart.
10. [用恶魔的声音]我要撕碎你的心脏。
- Mae wins.
- 梅赢了。
- Five items, gentlemen.
- 五样东西，先生们。
Five items that'll win that trophy for us.
五样东西，能帮我们赢得那个奖杯。
One: a bag of jelly beans.
第一：一袋软糖豆。
Two: some branches Dicky's gathering.
第二：迪基正在收集的一些树枝。
Three: a jar of cockroaches.
第三：一罐蟑螂。
Four: an oversized boxing glove.
第四：一只超大的拳击手套。
Five:
第五：
cottage cheese.
农家干酪。
[all cheering and clapping] - Yeah.
[所有人欢呼鼓掌] - 耶。
- That Teddy of Terror's finally gonna be ours this year.
今年，那个恐怖的泰迪终于要属于我们了。
- But I suggest you hide the jelly beans from Dicky.
但我建议你把豆子藏起来，别让迪基看见。
- Oh, yeah. Boy loves his beans.
哦，没错。那小子可喜欢豆子了。
- [sniffing]
（嗅）
I smell jelly beans.
我闻到了豆子的味道。
- No, you don't.
不，你没有。
- Whoa, dude, what happened to your arm?
哇，伙计，你的胳膊怎么了？
- Ah, the bush must've bit me.
啊，肯定是灌木丛咬了我。
- Bushes don't bite.
灌木丛不会咬人。
- You need to get out more, Ricky.
你得多出去走走，里基。
Well, I'm gonna go find myself a bandage.
好吧，我去找个绷带。
- Leave the sticks.
别管那些棍子了。
- Right.
好的。
- Okay, first part of our offense
好的，我们进攻的第一步
is a good defense.
是做好防守。
Who wants to go find out what the girls are up to?
谁想去看看女孩们在干什么？
- We got this.
我们搞得定。
- We've been eavesdropping all our lives.
我们一直都在偷听。
- Yeah.
没错。
We know what we hear.
我们知道我们听到了什么。
[upbeat music]
both: Hey, Mr. Harper. - [stammering] Hey.
两人齐声：嘿，哈珀先生。 - [结巴] 嘿。
Well, I was right.
好吧，我猜对了。
- Ha, looks like we both were, Edward Sticky-Hands.
- 哈，看来我们都猜对了，爱德华·粘手。
- This is no time to gloat, Anne, okay?
- 现在不是得意的时候，安妮，好吗？
I was just in the middle of telling you how right I was.
我正要告诉你我有多正确。
Those freeloading groomers next door
那些隔壁的寄生虫美容师
are using our dumpster.
正在使用我们的垃圾桶。
It's filled with pet clippings, chew toys,
里面装满了宠物剪毛、咀嚼玩具，
and this creepy doggy Halloween costume.
还有这件诡异的狗狗万圣节服装。
- I got bit by a bush.
- 我被灌木丛咬了一口。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Ah, don't worry. It's not real.
- 啊，别担心。这不是真的。
- No, no, I just caught a whiff of what I think might be Dicky.
- 不，不，我只是闻到了一股可能是Dicky的味道。
- Huh. Well, I didn't smell it.
- 嗯。我倒是没闻到。
Oh, there it is.
哦，在那里。
- Hello, ladies. - [gasps]
- 嗨，女士们。 - [惊呼]
Dicky, what are you doing in our area?
Dicky，你在这里做什么？
- Just looking for a bandage for this bite.
- 只是找个绷带来包扎这个咬伤。
all: Eww!
所有人: 咦！
- You smell like an ox...
- 你闻起来像头牛...
- Who burped up a goat...
- 谁打嗝吐出了一只羊...
- That ate a skunk.
- 那羊还吃了只臭鼬。
- If this is your way of telling me you like me,
- 如果这是你告诉我你喜欢我的方式，
you had me at, "Eww!"
你从那声“呃”开始就打动我了！
- Ugh!
- 呃！
- What was with Dicky's awful smell?
- Dicky那糟糕的气味是怎么回事？
- Ugh. I've smelled Dicky before,
- 呃。我以前也闻过Dicky的味道，
but never like that.
但从来没有这么糟糕。
- Do you think it's a part of the boy's scare?
- 你觉得这是男孩吓唬人的一部分吗？
[duct tape creaking]
[风管胶带吱吱作响]
- No.
不。
This is not part of any scare or any game.
这不是任何惊吓或游戏的一部分。
This is real.
这是真的。
- What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
- I've smelled this before.
我以前闻过这种味道。
It happened to my older brother.
我哥哥也遇到过这种情况。
This is no normal smell.
这不是普通的气味。
This smell
这种气味
will swallow ya whole.
会把你整个人吞噬掉。
- What caused it?
- 是什么引起的？
- He's changing.
- 他在变化。
all: He's changing?
所有人: 他在变化？
both: He's changing?
两人: 他在变化？
- He's changing.
- 他在变化。
One day, my brother was a regular annoying kid.
有一天，我哥哥还是个普通烦人的孩子。
The next day,
第二天，
he was a filthy animal.
他就变成了一个肮脏的动物。
That's exactly what's happening to Dicky.
这正是迪基正在经历的事情。
- Dicky's becoming a filthy animal?
- 迪基正在变成一个肮脏的动物？
- Oh, ah, ah!
哦，啊，啊！
[bang]
- [sighs] I can see you in there, Ricky.
我可以看到你在那里，Ricky。
- [creakily] No one in here but us squirrels.
这里没有别人，只有我们这些松鼠。
- [sighs] Come on, let's go some place private.
来吧，我们去个私密的地方。
So how did your brother become a filthy animal?
那么，你弟弟是怎么变成一个肮脏的动物的？
- Well, it started with him getting zits.
嗯，事情是从他长痘痘开始的。
- She said it started with him getting bit.
她说事情是从他被咬开始的。
Dicky got bit.
Dicky被咬了。
- By a bush.
被一丛灌木咬了。
- Yeah, but unless there was something inside that bush.
是的，但除非那丛灌木里有什么东西。
[gasps] Like the wild animal
像是那只四处游荡、吃女孩的野兽。
on the loose that's eating girls.
然后他总是感到饥饿。
- Then he got hungry all the time.
他就像个无底洞。
He was like a bottomless pit.
他吃了我们的父母……
He ate our parents...
他吃了他的父母。
- He ate his parents.
把家都吃空了。
- Out of house and home.
在他们家外面！
- Outside their home!
他已经变成了一个怪物。
- He had turned into a monster.
完全疯了。
A full-on loon. [all gasps]
一个彻头彻尾的疯子。[所有人都惊呼]
- They said he turned into a monster
- 他们说他变成了一个怪物
at the full moon.
在满月的时候。
This can only mean one thing.
这只能意味着一件事。
- Dicky...
- 迪基...
he's going through puberty.
他正在经历青春期。
[all shuddering]
[所有人都颤抖]
- Dicky...
- 迪基...
is becoming a werewolf!
正在变成狼人！
♪♪
- Dicky's turning into a werewolf?
Dicky变成狼人了？
Really? I think you're jumping to conclusions.
真的吗？我觉得你有点草率下结论了。
- [sighs] - Remember when we thought
记得我们以为
Mom and Dad turned into zombies?
爸爸妈妈变成了僵尸吗？
[roars]
（咆哮声）
- Get it together, man. We were young and foolish then.
振作点，伙计。那时候我们还年轻无知。
Zombies? That's kid stuff.
僵尸？那都是小孩子的玩意儿。
But everybody knows werewolves are real!
但大家都知道狼人是真的存在的！
- First, you know I don't respond well to being shaken!
首先，你知道我不喜欢被人摇晃！
And second, I'm going to need more proof.
其次，我需要更多的证据。
- Fine, you want more proof that werewolves exist?
好吧，你想知道更多证据证明狼人存在吗？
Ask Natlee's parents.
去问Natlee的父母。
Oh, wait. You can't!
哦，等等。你不能！
- What did I just say about the shaking?
我刚说了什么关于摇晃的事？
- Fine, you don't believe me?
好吧，你不相信我？
Would you believe your beloved Internet?
你会相信你亲爱的互联网吗？
- "Werewolves are humans who, after being bitten,
“狼人是被咬后，
"change into wolves during a full moon.
“在满月时变成狼的人类。
"Characteristics include rapid hair growth,
“特征包括快速毛发生长，
foul odor, extreme hunger"...
“恶臭，极度饥饿”...
- Bitten, hairy, smelly.
被咬了，毛茸茸的，臭臭的。
Dicky, Dicky, Dicky.
迪基，迪基，迪基。
- [scoffs] He hasn't been extremely hungry.
他还没到极度饥饿的地步。
- Okay, campers, hot dogs are ready.
好了，露营者们，热狗准备好了。
- Yes! I'm extremely hungry.
太好了！我非常饿。
[growls]
（咆哮声）
[grunting]
（咕噜声）
- Do you believe me now?
你现在相信我了吗？
I'm sorry!
对不起！
- I don't know.
我不知道。
- Ooh, hot!
哦，好烫！
[howling]
（嚎叫声）
- Dicky's becoming a werewolf!
迪基变成狼人了！
- We've got to tell Mom and Dad.
我们得告诉爸爸妈妈。
- Right! They'll know what to do.
对！他们会知道该怎么办。
[groans] Of course, if we tell Mom and Dad...
（呻吟）当然，如果我们告诉爸爸妈妈...
- They'll cancel the campout. - And the girls will keep
他们会取消露营活动。
the Teddy of Terror trophy for another year.
而女孩们会继续保留恐怖泰迪奖杯一年。
- [sighs]
（叹气）
Wait, do we really think
等等，我们真的认为
finally winning the Teddy of Terror trophy
终于赢得恐怖泰迪奖杯
is worth risking all of us being eaten?
值得我们冒着被吃掉的风险吗？
- Well, he probably can't eat all of us.
- 嗯，他可能吃不掉我们所有人。
- Yeah, I'll take those odds.
- 是的，我愿意接受这些几率。
- Hey, where are the hot dogs?
- 嘿，热狗在哪里？
- [in demonic voice] We couldn't get near them.
- 我们无法靠近它们。
- Please stop doing that.
- 请别再那样做了。
- Dicky was eating everything in sight.
- 迪基正在吃掉所有能看到的东西。
- Plus, he still smells...
- 而且，他仍然闻起来...
[in demonic voice] nasty.
很恶心。
Last one, sorry.
最后一个，抱歉。
- Okay, that's it.
好吧，就这样。
If we're gonna make it through this campout,
如果我们想顺利完成这次露营，
Dawn, you're gonna have to give Dicky this.
Dawn，你得把这个给Dicky。
- But what is it?
但这是什么？
- Silver Bullet deodorant spray.
银子弹牌除臭喷雾。
It's the only thing that worked for my brother.
这是我哥哥唯一用过有效的。
- But why do I have to give it to him?
但为什么我得给他？
- Because you're his sister.
因为你是他姐姐。
Plus... both: Not it!
再加上... 我们都：不是我！
- Why am I always it?
- 为什么总是我？
Why do you even have this in your bag anyway?
- 你为什么会在包里放这个？
- I grabbed my brother's wrestling bag by mistake.
- 我误拿了哥哥的摔跤包。
- That explains your pajamas.
- 这就解释了你的睡衣。
- Ugh.
- 呃。
But--but Dicky stinks.
- 但是迪基很臭。
You do it.
- 你来做。
- [in demonic voice] I said, "Not it."
- [用恶魔般的声音] 我说了，“不是我。”
- Ugh!
- 呃！
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Hey. - Nope.
- So it says here that the only way to stop a werewolf
is a silver bullet.
- [groans] Silver bullet?
Where are we gonna get one of those?
- I don't know. - Hey, guys. [giggles]
Now, I'm not sure if you've noticed,
but there's something going on with Dicky.
He, um...
Give him this.
- Huh. Silver Bullet.
- 啊。银色子弹。
- Comes in spray form.
- 有喷雾形式的。
That's convenient.
那很方便。
- All right, kids, gather around.
- 好了，孩子们，围过来。
The full moon is out.
满月出来了。
[all clapping and cheering]
[所有人鼓掌欢呼]
- Full moon?
- 满月？
Dicky could change any minute.
迪基随时可能变身。
We've got to do something.
我们得做点什么。
- I've got an idea.
- 我有个主意。
- [gasps] Ooh, a jelly bean.
- [倒吸一口气] 哦，一颗软糖豆。
Ooh, ooh.
哦，哦。
Oh.
哦。
Hey.
嘿。
- Listen, this isn't easy to say,
- 听着，这话不容易说出口，
but-- - There's no tutti-frutti?
但-- - 没有水果味吗？
- No, worse. You're turning into a werewolf.
- 不，更糟。你正在变成狼人。
- [gasps] I thought you said worse!
- [倒吸一口气] 我还以为你说更糟的呢！
- Werewolves eat human beings.
- 狼人会吃人。
- So, for everyone's safety, we're locking you
- 所以，为了大家的安全，我们今晚要把你锁在这里。
in here over night. - What?
在这里过夜。 - 什么？
- Here. Spray this on yourself
- 这里。开始变化时，把这个喷在自己身上。
when you start the change.
- 等等，什么？
- Wait. What?
不，我不想变成狼人。
No, I don't want to be a werewolf.
- 放松。
- Relax.
你早上就会变回来的。
You'll change back in the morning.
在那之前，一整袋的水果糖。
Until then, an entire bag of tutti-frutti.
- 哦。
- Ooh.
- 听着，Mae。我一直在想。
- Listen, Mae. I've been thinking.
如果Dicky正在经历变化，那么这是否意味着我也可能很快会经历同样的变化？
If changes are happening to Dicky,
如果Dicky正在经历变化，
then doesn't that mean they could happen to me soon too?
那是不是意味着我也很快会经历这些变化呢？
I mean, we are the exact same age.
我是说，我们同龄。
- [laughs] Dawn, relax.
Dawn，放松点。
My mom says it happens at different times
我妈说每个人发生这些变化的时间不同。
for different people.
我还没经历呢。
It hasn't happened to me yet.
可能你还要等一段时间。
Maybe it won't happen to you for a while.
哦，太好了。我只是有点担心
- Oh, good. I was worried
因为我腿上开始长了一点毛发。
just 'cause I have a little bit of hair growing on my legs.
一点点毛发说明不了什么。
- A little bit of hair doesn't mean anything.
一点点毛发并不代表什么。
Let's take a look.
让我们看看。
Well, you have to pull down your socks so I can see.
嗯，你得把袜子拉下来，我才能看到。
- I'm not wearing socks.
我没穿袜子。
- Oh.
哦。
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
Ugh, this is all so confusing and embarrassing.
呃，这一切都太令人困惑和尴尬了。
I mean, there's so many boys here.
我是说，这里这么多男孩。
What if they see?
如果他们看到了怎么办？
- They can't see what's not there.
他们看不到不存在的东西。
- Of course! Perfect.
当然！完美。
- Uh, you know how to do this, right?
呃，你知道怎么做的，对吧？
- How hard can it be?
这能有多难？
[howling]
[嚎叫]
- Is that Dawn?
那是Dawn吗？
- Do you think she's changing too?
你觉得她也在变吗？
- [gasps]
[喘气]
- Are you okay?
你还好吗？
- What happened to your leg?
你的腿怎么了？
- Uh, b-d-d--nothing. I--
呃，没-没什么。我--
- Uh, got bit.
呃，被咬了。
- Yeah, no biggie.
是啊，没什么大不了的。
- [gasps]
（惊呼）
- Oh, it's a biggie.
哦，这可是大事。
She got bit, just like Dicky!
她被咬了，就像迪基一样！
- We're going to need a bigger vault!
我们需要一个更大的保险库！
[both screaming]
（两人尖叫）
- [whistling]
（吹口哨）
- Ricky, I got your text! What do you want?
瑞奇，我收到你的短信了！你想要什么？
[sighs] Look, if this is your lame attempt to scare me,
听着，如果这是你拙劣的吓唬我的尝试，
I'm not in the mood, and it's not working.
我现在没心情，这招也不管用。
- This isn't about the scare.
这不是关于吓唬你的事。
We know what's really happening to you.
我们知道你真正发生了什么。
- [chuckles nervously] What are you talking about?
你到底在说什么？
I'm totally normal hairless Dawn.
我完全正常的，无毛的Dawn。
- Come on, we're quads.
拜托，我们是四胞胎。
You can't hide stuff like this from us.
你不能对我们隐瞒这种事。
- [sighs] Okay, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Look, I didn't want this to happen,
听着，我并不希望这事发生，
but it's happening, and I don't know what to do.
但它确实发生了，我不知道该怎么办。
- Don't worry. We love you.
- 别担心。我们爱你。
We're here for you, and we're going to help you.
我们在这里支持你，我们会帮助你。
- Aww, that's so sweet.
- 哦，真贴心。
- But we're not going to touch you.
- 但我们不会碰你。
- Except to do this!
- 除了这样做！
Ha. - What are you guys doing?
哈。- 你们在干什么？
Let me out of here! - Stay away.
让我出去！- 离远点。
- Dicky? - I mean it.
- 迪基？- 我是认真的。
Don't come any closer. - Trust me, I'm not.
别再靠近了。- 相信我，我不会的。
I'm not going anywhere near you.
我不会靠近你。
- I don't blame you.
- 我不怪你。
I'm a monster.
我是个怪物。
- I know.
- 我知道。
Look, and don't tell anyone, but...
听着，别告诉任何人，但是...
I'm going through the same thing you are.
我正在经历和你一样的事情。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
Stay away from me, you vile beast!
离我远点，你这可恶的野兽！
- Stop it! I don't smell!
- 别说了！我又不臭！
- Smell? This is to stop you
- 臭？这是为了阻止你
from changing into a werewolf!
变成狼人！
- A werewolf?
狼人？
That is deodorant, Dicky,
那是除臭剂，Dicky，
to keep you from smelling.
为了防止你身上有异味。
You're not turning into a werewolf.
你不会变成狼人的。
You're turning into...
你正在变成……
a man.
一个男人。
- A man? Sweet.
男人？太好了。
[growling]
[咆哮]
- What are you doing?
你在做什么？
- Becoming a man.
在成为一个男人。
This is what men do.
这就是男人所做的。
[growls] Come on, growl with me.
来吧，跟我一起吼。
- No. - If I'm becoming a man,
- 不要。- 如果我要成为男人，
you're becoming a woman.
你也得成为女人。
Give me a woman growl. - No.
给我一个女性的吼声。- 不要。
- Come on. [growls]
- 来吧。[吼叫]
If I have to go through this, you do too.
如果我得经历这个，你也要。
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
[growls meekly]
[弱弱地吼叫]
- Come on, woman, you can do better than that.
- 加油，女人，你可以做得比这更好。
- [growls meekly] - [growls]
- [低声咆哮] - [咆哮]
- [growls] - [growls]
- [咆哮] - [咆哮]
[both growling]
[两人都在咆哮]
- Whoo, we locked them in there just in time.
- 哇，我们刚好及时把他们锁在里面了。
- Oh, yeah.
- 哦，没错。
[both growling]
[两人都在咆哮]
- Okay, this is weird.
- 好吧，这有点奇怪。
But thank you. Now help me look for a way out.
但谢谢你。现在帮我找找出去的路。
- Hey, there's a vent.
- 嘿，那里有个通风口。
- We can climb out.
- 我们可以爬出去。
- [grunts] - Okay.
- [咕噜声] - 好吧。
But before we get in that very small space together,
但在我们挤进那个非常小的空间之前，
you need some Silver Bullet.
你需要一些银弹。
[gags]
[作呕声]
Why is this stuff so sticky?
这东西为什么这么黏？
Dicky, this isn't Silver Bullet.
迪基，这不是银弹。
This is the spray glue Dad used to decorate the store.
这是爸爸用来装饰店铺的喷胶。
- Oops.
- 哎呀。
- Okay, whatever. Just forget it.
- 好吧，随便了。忘了它吧。
Now let's get out of here.
现在让我们离开这里。
- [grunts] [snaps fingers]
- [咕哝声] [打响指]
Where do you think this vent leads?
你觉得这个通风口通向哪里？
- Probably somewhere in the store.
- 可能通向店里的某个地方。
Come on.
快点。
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
[crash]
[撞击声]
Or into a dumpster.
或者通向一个垃圾桶。
- Oh, no-no-no, Squishy.
- 哦，不不不，Squishy。
No more hot dogs for you. [dog growls]
你不能再吃热狗了。[狗低吼]
You've already got some nasty wiener toots.
你已经有够糟糕的热狗屁了。
[dog whimpers]
[狗发出呜咽声]
- Have you guys seen Dawn?
- 你们有谁见过Dawn吗？
We've got a Teddy of Terror to win and she's disappeared.
我们有个恐怖泰迪熊要赢，她却不见了。
- I haven't seen her. Have you seen her?
- 我没看到她。你看到她了吗？
- Seen who? - Dawn.
- 看到谁？ - Dawn。
- Dawn who? - Dawn who?
- Dawn是谁？ - Dawn是谁？
- You know darn well Dawn who.
- 你明明知道Dawn是谁。
- Something strange is going on here,
- 这里有些奇怪的事情发生，
'cause we can't find Dicky either.
因为我们连Dicky也找不到了。
- That's it. We gotta tell them.
- 就是这样。我们得告诉他们。
Dicky and Dawn were bitten and are turning into werewolves.
迪基和道恩被咬了，正在变成狼人。
- Come on, we're on the same team, remember?
- 拜托，我们是一队的，记得吗？
- Yeah, why are you trying to scare us?
- 是啊，你为什么要吓我们？
- Oh, please, we're not buying this little
- 哦，拜托，我们可不吃这套
"you're even scaring us" routine.
“你甚至吓到我们了”的小把戏。
- Yeah, and everyone knows
- 是啊，而且大家都知道
there's no such thing as werewolves.
根本就没有狼人这种东西。
[both groaning]
[两人呻吟]
all: Werewolves!
所有人：狼人！
- That way.
- 那边。
- [in demonic voice] I'm gonna rip out your heart.
- [恶魔般的声音] 我要撕裂你的心脏。
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
both: Cockroaches!
两人: 蟑螂!
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
[clang]
[铛]
[whoosh and thud]
[呼啸和砰]
[splatting]
[啪嗒声]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Yes!
是的!
It worked!
成功了!
- Come on, guys. It's just us--ow.
- 来吧，伙计们。就我们几个——哎哟。
- We're not monsters.
- 我们不是怪物。
[both groaning and howling]
[两人呻吟和嚎叫]
- Guys, what is going on?
- 伙计们，这是怎么回事？
- We accidentally sprayed ourselves with glue--ah--
- 我们不小心把自己喷上了胶水——啊——
and then fell into the dumpster.
- 然后掉进了垃圾桶。
- And it's filled with dog hair.
- 而且里面全是狗毛。
- Aha!
- 啊哈！
- And dog collars...
- 还有狗项圈...
[both howling]
[两人嚎叫]
all: Ohh...
哦...
- Wait, but what about Natlee's brother?
等等，那Natlee的哥哥呢？
We heard you through the vent.
我们通过通风口听到你们说话。
You said he got bitten and ate your parents
你说他在外面咬了你父母，然后吃了他们。
outside your home.
我是说他长了痘痘，把家里的食物都吃光了。
- I said he got zits and ate my parents
把他赶出了家门。
out of house and home.
嗯，这样就合理多了。
- Huh. Well, that makes more sense.
他只是在成长而已。
- He was just maturing.
就像我们现在开始的一样。
Just like we're starting to.
就像你们将来也会一样。
Just like you all will.
就像你们所有人都会经历的那样。
all: Cool!
太棒了！
- It was pretty funny, though.
不过，那真的很搞笑。
You guys should've seen the looks on your faces.
你们真该看看你们当时的表情。
- Yeah, you were all like...
是啊，你们当时都那样……
- We weren't all like...
我们并不是都那样……
- Yeah, we're way too old to be all like...
是啊，我们都太老了，不该那样……
over something so childish.
对这么幼稚的事情。
all: Spider!
蜘蛛！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪